HENRY KOFI BRANDOH

- brandohhenry@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in//henry-kofi-brandoh-4316b6138/
- https://www.henryhkb.github.io/myprofile

OBJECTIVE

I seek an opportunity to serve and excel in any assigned role as my skills and abilities may merit. I look forward to sharing my problem-solving skills and experience to mass up more knowledge and skills from wherever I find myself.

EDUCATION

Ghana Communication Technology University

September 2016 - June 2020

BSc Information Communication Technology

Ghana National College November 2013 - May 2016

General Arts

SKILLS

Software Development/Programming: PHP, JavaScript, Laravel,

Electronics: Arduino

Cyber Security: Website Penetration Testing

Others: Git, Linux, Photoshop, Database(MySQL)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Library Assistant (Ghana Communication Technology University)

September 2016 – Present

- Assisting graduate students in getting relevant books for their research.
- Seeing to it that the graduate library was kept in good shape at all times.
- Assisting the graduate students in research for their project work.

Intern Software Systems Unit (Ghana Technology University)

September 2018 – December 2018

• I came up with ways of improving the school's website by recommending other functionalities that could be added to increase the content and provide more information to viewers.

Summer Intern (The Trust Hospital - Mother and Child)

May 2018 – August 2018

• I was an Information Technology assistant offering support to users in various departments facing challenges with their computers, software and networking issues of the hospital.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- I participated in Facebook developer circles where my team and I created a common College Application for high school students in Ghana. This was to eradicate the manual process of buying and filling out college applications.
- I participated in a hackathon organized by MEST. (Meltwater Entrepreneurship of Technology) where my team and I placed third position. We created a hospital application to help doctors in diagnosing and prescribing drugs to their patients based on passed medical records.
- Udacity Frontend Web developer course.
- Master the Mainframe Competition.

REFEREES

Mr. Kenneth Azumah

Head of Hospital Information Systems

Email: <u>Kazumah@thetrusthospital.com</u>

Mrs. Benedicta K. A. Bitherman

E-Resources Librarian

Email: bkrampah@gtuc.edu.gh